[
  {
    "front": "Ela/Ele (üë©/üë®)",
    "back": "zij",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Sol (üåû)",
    "back": "zon",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Gostaria, deveria (ü§∑‚Äç‚ôÇÔ∏è)",
    "back": "zou",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Irm√£ (üë©‚Äçü¶∞)",
    "back": "zus",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "oito",
    "back": "acht",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.802Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "carro",
    "back": "auto",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.802Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "trabalho, emprego",
    "back": "baan",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.802Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "beb√™",
    "back": "baby",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.802Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "estouro, bang",
    "back": "bang",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.802Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "banco",
    "back": "bank",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.802Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "perna",
    "back": "been",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.802Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "urso",
    "back": "beer",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.802Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "montanha",
    "back": "berg",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "melhor, √≥timo",
    "back": "best",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "folha",
    "back": "blad",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "feliz",
    "back": "blij",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "livro",
    "back": "boek",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "√°rvore",
    "back": "boom",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "feij√£o",
    "back": "boon",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "bravo, zangado",
    "back": "boos",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  }
]